A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness House drawings, SG 2 FA247
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fourth Floor, 1906-1984; 6
  - Building/Floor Plans, 6.1
    - Chamber No. 6
      - 2/5/1908, 390 NY 33 (Folder 157)
        Chamber No. 6, East Elevation, North Elevation, # 1-30 1/4"x14 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-30 1/8"x14 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - undated, P-4, 729 (Folder 158)
        South Elevation of Chamber No. 6, 17"x13", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
      - undated, P-5, 730 (Folder 158)
        East Elevation of Chamber No. 6, 15 1/4"x12 13/16", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
      - undated, P-6, 731 (Folder 158)
        West Elevation of Chamber No. 6, 14 7/8"x12 3/8", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
      - undated, P-7, 732 (Folder 158)
        North Elevation of Chamber No. 6, 17 1/8"x12 7/8", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
      - undated, No Number Listed (Full P # -Torn Off) (Folder 158)
        Plan of Chamber No.6, 18 1/4"x18 1/2", Paper, Architects, N/A, (Probably Pottier and Stymus Co.)
    - Sewing Room
      - 2/5/1908, 391 NY 33 (Folder 159)
        Sewing Room, Plan, East Elevation, West Elevation, # 1-30 1/2"x14 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-30 1/2"x14 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 392 NY 33 (Folder 159)
        Sewing Room, North Elevation, South Elevation, # 1-30 1/2"x14 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-30 1/4"x14 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 159)
        Sewing Room, 23 7/8"x19 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
        Received 7/14/1908 Charles T. Wills
    - Hall/Stair Hall
      - 2/5/1908, 393 NY 33 (Folder 160)
        East Corridor in Fourth Story, # 1-30 1/8"x15", Tracing Paper, # 2-20 1/8"x15", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 394 NY 33 (Folder 160)
        East Corridor, Fourth Story, North Elevation, # 1-30"x15", Tracing Paper, # 2-30"x15", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 395 NY 33 (Folder 160)
        East Corridor in Fourth Story, West Elevation and East Elevation, # 1-28 5/8"x15", Tracing Paper, # 2-28 1/2"x15", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 396 NY 33 (Folder 161)
        West Corridor, Fourth Story, General Notes on the Right Side, #1-29 1/8"x15 3/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-29 1/4"x15 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 397 NY 33 (Folder 161)
        West Corridor, Fourth Story, East Elevation, North Elevation, # 1-29 7/8"x15", Tracing Paper, # 2-29 7/8"x14 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 398 NY 33 (Folder 161)
        West Corridor, Fourth Story, West Elevation, South Elevation, # 1-29 1/2"x15", Tracing Paper, # 2-29 5/8"x15", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 1981 December 11, 399-2 NY 33 (Folder 162)
        Plan of Stair Hall, Ceiling, Fourth Story, Sec "B-B", "D-D", # 1-20 1/2x16 3/4", Tracing Paper, #2-20 1/2"x16 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 1981 December 11, 912 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 36 Second Copy Doesn't Have an Office # (Folder 162)
        Plan and Elevation of Fourth Floor Stair Hall, (2 Copies) # 1-29 1/2"x18 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, ... (Tr)aitel's-... (dr)rawing, No. 36,...an and..., ... (el)evations of.. (fo)urth stair (parts were cut off due to the corners being cut), 29"x15 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
        #1-4/28/1908 #2-4/28/1908, Revised 5/16/1908
      - undated, 1077 (Office Copy) (Folder 162)
        Plan of the Fourth Floor, 25 5/8"x16", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers)
      - 7/15/1908, 1090 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 62 Second Copy Doesn't Have an Office Copy # (Folder 163)
        Plan of Marble Base and Plinth Blocks, West Corridor, Fourth Floor, # 1-21 1/2"x10 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Base for West Corridor, 4th Floor, 21 1/8"x10 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - 7/16/1908, 1091 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 73 Second Copy Doesn't Have an Office Copy # (Folder 163)
        Plan of Marble Base, East Corridor, Fourth Floor, Full Scale Detail of Base Blocks, Section of the Base, # 1-Written on the Back in Pencil, Marble Base 4th Fl, 30"x16 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, East Corridor, 4 Floor, 29 1/4"x17 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
  - HVAC, 6.2
    - 10/5/1982, AC-4, Job Number 26-82 (Folder 164)
      Proposed Air Conditioning System, Fourth Floor, 36 1/2"x20", Sepia Tone, Architects, P and O Air Control Co., Inc.
    - 4/9/1907, No Number Listed (Folder 164)
      Fourth Story Plan, Notes on the Bottom, It's a Copy, Paper Size-26"x18 1/4", Image Size-23 3/8"x12 1/2", Paper, Architects, N/A
  - Plumbing, 6.3
    - 6/5/1978, 049-01, A-2 (Folder 165)
      Proposed Alterations Fourth Floor, Plumbing Riser Diagram, (Commonwealth Fund) 36 1/2"x19", Paper (Blue Ink), Architects, Francis Day Rogers
    - 4/15/1907, 1369 (Folder 165)
      Plumbing Plans, Fourth Story Plan, # 1-36 1/2"x16 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-It's a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-20 1/4"x9", Paper, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
  - Electrical, 6.4
    - 8/24/1962, F-1 (Revision) (Folder 166)
      Revision: In Furniture Layout, Electrical and Telephone Outlet, Location of Carson, Lundin and Shaw, 18"x23", Black and White (Blue Print), Architects, Carson, Lundin and Shaw
    - 11/10/1984, Revised 12/9/1984; No Number Listed (Folder 166)
      Milbank Fund, Furniture Plan with New Electrical, 36 1/8"x24", Paper, Architects, N/A
- Fifth Floor, 1906-1983; 7
  - Building/Floor Plan, 7.1
    - 11/8/1906, 6 NY 33 (Folder 167)
      Fifth Floor Plan, 42"x21 7/8", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 4/29/1907, Revised 2/4/1908; 105 NY 33 (Folder 168)
      Fifth Story Plan, Roof Plan and Penthouse Roof Plan, # 1-41 7/8"x32 1/2", Linen, # 2-42 1/8"x32 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-41 1/8"x321/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 4-41 3/4"x32 1/4", Paper (Blue Ink), # 5-42 3/4"x32 3/4", Polyester Paper, # 6-21 1/4"x16 3/4", Paper (Photocopier paper), Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Servants' Rooms
      - 11/6/1907, 308 NY 33 (Folder 169)
        Detail of Wardrobes and Closets in Fifth Story, Detail of Wardrobe in Servants Room No. 6-Wardrobes in Other Rooms Similar, Elevation of Wardrobe A, Section A-A, Plan, Elevation of Linen Closet B, Section B-B, Plan, Elevation of Cedar Closet C, Section C-C, Plan, Elevation in Laundry D, Section D-D, Plan, 41"x19", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Laundry
      - 8/8/1907, 203 NY 33 (Folder 170)
        Section Through Top of East Laundry Wall, 13 1/2"x15", Tracing Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 7/9/1908, 399-8 NY 33 (Folder 170)
        Copper Pan for Washer in Laundry, Section Near Center, Section at Each End, Full Scale Section at "A-A", # 1-21 3/4"x15 1/2", Linen, # 2-21 5/8"x15 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 3/29/1907-4/13/1907, 1363 (Folder 170)
        Detail of Drain Connection for Laundry Washer Pan, #1-14 3/4"x17 7/8", Linen, # 2-14 3/8"x17 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-17 3/4"x14 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
        3/29/1907 #3-Laund Dr. Added 4/13/1907
    - Hall/Stair Hall
      - undated, 792 (Office Copy) (Folder 171)
        Stair from Fifth Floor to Attic, 15"x12 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A (Hale and Rogers)
        Received 3/29/1908 Charles T. Wills, 3/31/1908 Hale and Rogers
  - HVAC, 7.2
    - 10/5/1982, AC-5, Job Number 26-82 (Folder 172)
      Proposed Air Conditioning System, Fifth Floor, 36 1/2"x20", Sepia Tone, Architects, P and O Air Control Co., Inc.
    - 5/24/1983, M-5 (Folder 173)
      Alterations to HVAC System, HVAC-Fifth Floor Reflected Ceiling Plan and Fifth Floor Electric Plan, HVAC and Electric-Attic Floor Plan, Electric-Part Plan Attic Floor, 49 1/2"x30 1/4", Paper, Architects, Stramandinoli, Mellusi and Khlyavich
    - 4/9/1907, No Number Listed (Folder 172)
      Fifth Story Plan, Notes on the Bottom, It's a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-23 1/8"x12 1/2", Paper, Architects, N/A
  - Plumbing, 7.3
    - 4/15/1907, 1370 (Folder 174)
      Plumbing Plans, Fifth Story Plan, # 1-36 1/2"x15 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-It's a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-20 3/8"x9", Paper, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
  - Electrical, 7.4
    - 6/30/1978, Revised 8/23/1978; Job Number 049-02, A3 (Folder 175)
      Proposed Alterations Fifth Floor (Milbank Foundation), 35 3/8"x19", Paper, Architects, Francis Day Rogers
    - 12/28/1950-2/2/1953, Job Number 421, Drawing Number 4 (Folder 176-177)
      Alteration to One East 75th St N.Y.C. for the Commonwealth Fund, Fifth Floor and Roof Plans, Section "A-A", Section "B-B", # 1-Written on the Back in Pencil, Telephone, Layouts 1/6/1952, Written on the Back in Marker, Telephone, 1/25/1951-New Stair to the Roof, 4/10/1951-Owner Requests-DV Removed, 4/23/1951-Plumbing and General Notes Added, 5/16/1951-Owner Requests, 5/22/1951-Exist. Lav. Retained-Office 5/12, 42 1/8"x26", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Electrical (Stamped), 41 1/2"x26", Paper, # 3-Has the Architects Pencil Notations, 41 5/8"x26 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 4-No Electrical Stamp, Written on the Back in Pencil, Copy # 3, First Alteration, Electrical, 12/28/50, 4/10/51, 41 5/8"x26 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 5-Electrical (Stamped), Written on the Back in Pen, Electrical Alterations, 1950-52, 42"x26", Diazo Blue Print, # 6-Electrical (Stamped), 42"x26", Diazo Blue Print, # 7-Electrical-Revised: 6/1951-Outlets Added in Space Nos. 5-3,5-6, 5-8, 5-13, Switch Added in Space No. 5-15, Outlet Omitted in Space No. 5-5, 2/2/1953-Revised as per Contractors Marked Up Drawings, 43 7/8"x27 7/8", Linen (Blue), # 8-1/25/1951-New Stair to Roof, Written on the Back in Pen, Roll 2, Proposed Office Alterations 1951, 42"x26", Paper (Blue Ink), Architects, # 1-Rogers and Butler, # 2-Rogers and Butler, Clifton E. Smith and Edward B. Silverman, Consulting Electrical Engineers, # 3-4-Rogers and Butler, # 5-7-Rogers and Butler, Clifton E. Smith and Edward B. Silverman, Consulting Electrical Engineers, # 8-Rogers and Butler.
      #1-12/28/1950 #2-Revised 6/26/1951 #3-Revised 6/26/1951 #4-Revised 1/25/1951, 4/10/1951 #5-Revised 6/26/1951, 2/2/1953 #6-Revised 6/26/1951 #7-Revised 6/26/1951, 2/2/1953 #8-Revised 1/25/51
      #2-Received 2/3/1953 Rogers and Butler #3-Received 7/3/1951 Rogers and Butler #5-Received 2/3/1953 Rogers and Butler #6-Received 7/3/1951 Rogers and Butler
    - 3/28/1908, Order Number 2047, 1824/5 (Folder 175)
      Power Panel -B- 5th Floor, Iron Lined Wood Box, 19 1/2"x11 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, H. Krantz Manufacturing Co.
    - 3/14/1908, Order Number 2047, 1824/7 (Folder 175)
      Panel -A- Fifth Floor, Iron Lined Wood Box, 10 3/4"x11 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, H. Krantz Manufacturing Co.
- Roof/Pent House Roof, 1907-1985; 8
  - Building/Floor Plans, 8.1
    - 4/29/1907, 112 NY 33 (Folder 178)
      Attic Floor Framing Plan, Roof Framing Plan, Pent House Roof Framing Plan, Elevation of Trusses C, F, and G, (Truss Diagram) Truss A, B, D and E, H, End of Truss F and G, Section Thro' Pent House-Looking North, Section Thro' Pent House Looking West, # 1-42"x32 1/4", Linen, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Residence ESH, 4/29/07, Prints #101, 109, 110,111, 112, 42"x32 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 3/17/1908, 718 (Office Copy), Order Number 1770, Plan Number 17 (Folder 179)
      Pent House Roof Carpenter Plan Section B-B, Fan Room Floor Carpenter Plan, Raining Plan Section A-A, Framing Plan, 21 5/8"x14 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hennibique Construction Co., Armored Concrete Constructions
    - 4/6/1985, A-3 Prel. (Folder 178)
      Exterior Facade and Roof Renovations, Roof Plan, 42 3/8"x32 1/2", Paper, Architects, Vincent Stramandinoli and Associates
    - Brass Railing
      - 3/17/1922, 201 NY 376 (Folder 180)
        Details of Brass Railing on Roof, Elevation, 75th Street Scale of Roof Plan, Scale of Sections Showing Railing, Braces, Full Size Details Front View, 35 1/2"x19 7/8", Linen, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
    - Cedar Tank
      - undated, 743 (Office Copy) (Folder 180)
        White Cedar House Tank for Roof, Plan of Tank, Elevation of Tank, Detail of Corners of Tank, 18 3/4"x12 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, J.N. Knight and Son, Plumbers
        Received 3/23/1908 Charles T. Wills, 3/24/1908 Hale and Rogers, Corrected 3/28/1908 Hale and Rogers
    - Chimney
      - 9/14/1909, 206 NY 33 (Folder 180)
        Scale Drawing of Iron Brace for East Chimney, Note on the Bottom, 19 3/4"x14 3/4", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A (Probably Hale and Rogers)
      - undated, 1202 (Office Copy) (Folder 181)
        Proposed Alterations to Chimneys Stacks A-E, North Elevation, South Elevation, East Elevation and West Elevation and Plan at "X", # 1-36 3/4"x@ 29 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-36 5/8"x@ 29 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, B.A. and G.N. Williams Cut Stone
        #1-Approved 8/23/1909 Hale and Rogers #2-Received 9/12/1909 Charles T. Wills, 9/3/1909 Haleand Rogers
      - 1/30/1908, No Number Listed (Folder 180)
        (No Title) Furnish One Flue Like This, See Full Size Detail of Terra Cotta Flues and C.I. Thimble, 23 5/8"x22 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
      - 1/27/1922, No Number Listed (Folder 180)
        One Portable Ladder for 3 Chimneys, Ordered from Sloane and Moller 2/14/1922, 12 1/4"x10", Tracing Paper, Architects, James Gamble Rogers
    - Sky Lights
      - 8/21/1951, Drawing Number 1A, Reference to Drawing Number 4 (Office Copy) (Folder 181)
        The Commonwealth Fund Alterations, Skylight Details, Frame, Straight Bar, Ridge Bar and Vent, Plan, Notes, Written on the Back in Pen, Skylights, 40 3/4"x30", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, A. Munder and Son, Inc.
  - HVAC, 8.2
    - 5/24/1983, M-6 (Folder 182)
      Alterations to HVAC System, Demolition of Attic Floor, Detail of Base Support for Cooling Tower, Detail of Chilled Water Riser Anchors, Detail of Typical Insulated Pipe Support, 49 1/2"x30 1/4", Paper, Architects, Stramandinoli, Mellusi and Khlyavich
    - 4/9/1907, No Number Listed (Folder 183)
      Roof Plan, Elevation at Truss G, Detail of Frames for Fans, Section Through Penthouse Looking West, Section Through Penthouse Looking North, Details Showing Dampers in Smoke Flues, Written on the Back in Pencil, Plumbing Plans, It's a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-23 1/4"x12 1/2", Paper, Architects, N/A
  - Plumbing, 8.3
    - 4/15/1907, 1371 (Folder 184)
      Plumbing Plans, Roof Story Plan, # 1-36 1/2"x15 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-It's a Copy, Paper Size, 24"x18 1/4", Image Size-20"x8 3/4", Paper, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
- Other, 1907-1985; 9
  - Elevators, 9.1
    - 2/15/1908-2/13/1908, 114 NY 33 (Folder 185)
      Drawing of Elevator Skylights, Etc., Revised North Elevation of Pent House, Section Through Top of the Service Elevator Shaft, Looking West, Section Through Top of Passenger Elevator Shaft, Looking West, Plan of Part of Attic and Pent House, Part of Roof Plan Showing Changes, # 1-35 1/8"x27", Linen, # 2-34 3/4"x24", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-35 1/8"x27", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      #1 and #2-2/15/1908 #3-2/13/1908
    - 10/19/1907, 307 NY 33 (Folder 185)
      Scale Details of Supports for Sheave Beams, Elevation of Support for Sheave Beams Passenger Elevator, Elevation of Support for Sheave Beams Service Elevator, 15 3/8"x18 1/2", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 12/27/1907, 317 NY 33 (Folder 185)
      Scale Drawing of Passenger Elevator Car, Plan of Ceiling, Plan of Floor, Rear Elevation, Front Elevation, Side Elevation, 26"x21", Tracing Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 4/30/1908, 399-4 NY 33 (Folder 186)
      Steel Service Elevator Car, Plan of Car, North Elevation of Car, West Elevation of Car, Detail of Screen (Full Size), # 1-29 3/8"x23", Linen, # 2-29 1/4"x23", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 3/1/1908, 715 (Office Copy) (Folder 187)
      Trims and Jambs to Passenger Elevator on First, Second, and Third Floors, Full Size Section Thro the Five Bronze Thresholds Passenger Elevator Door Openings, 1st Floor, 2nd Floor, 3rd Floor, 4th Floor, 24 1/4"x46 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - undated, 924 (Office Copy) (Folder 188)
      North Elevation of Elevator Enclosure, West Elevation of Elevator Enclosure, Plan of Basement Floor, Plan of First Floor, Plan of Platform Between First and Second Floors, Plan of Second Floor, Drawing Showing Saddle and Sheet Iron Fascine on Basement Floor, Drawing Showing Fastening of 2" Square Bars to Beams, Detail at Section "A-A", Detail at Section "B-B", Detail at Section "C-C", 35 1/2"x48 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
      Received 5/11/1908 Charles T. Wills, 5/19/1908 Hale and Rogers
    - 5/11/1908, Revised 5/16/1908; 925 (Office Copy), Contract Number 2810, Drawing Number H-577-3 (Folder 186)
      Service Elevator, Revised Swing of Doors, 16 5/8"x16", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Otis Elevator Company
    - undated, 935 (Office Copy) (Folder 188)
      North Elevation of Elevator Enclosure, West Elevation of Elevator Enclosure, Plans of Elevator Enclosures, Plan of Mezzo Floor, Plan of Third Floor, Plan of Fourth Floor, Plan of Fifth Floor, Plan of Attic, Scale Detail of Sheet Iron Ledge, Scale Detail Section Through Saddle on Mezzanine Floor, Scale Detail Showing Fastening of Uprights, Scale Detail of Section Through Saddle 3rd Floor, Scale Detail of Section Through Saddle on 5th Floor, 37 5/8"x@ 59", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
      Received 5/18/1908 Charles T. Wills, 5/12 and 19/1908 Hale and Rogers
    - 5/9/1908, 940 (Office Copy) (Folder 189)
      Saddles for Passenger Elevator, 1st Floor Plan, 2nd Floor Plan, Mezzanine Plan, 3rd Floor Plan, 4th Floor Plan, 43"x25 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
    - undated, 1033 (Office Copy), O.B. 2723 - Second Copy Doesn't Have an Office # (Folder 187)
      Detail of Sheet Iron Enclosure Around Elevator Machinery in Pent House, Plan, Elevation Looking North, Section Through "A-A" Looking East, # 1-33 1/4"x28 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-@ 28 1/4"x34 3/8, Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Wlliams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
      Received 6/28/1908 Charles T. Wills, Approved 6/24/1908 Hale and Rogers
    - undated, Contract Number 2810 (Folder 190)
      Passenger Elevator, @ 22 1/2"x29 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Otis Elevator Company
      Received 11/6/1907
    - 1/31/1908, Contract Number 2810, Drawing Number H-577-2 (Folder 191)
      One Service Elevator, Cellar Plan, Sectional Elevation, Plan, Notes on Right Side, 23 1/2"x22 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Otis Elevator Company
    - 12/1/1950, Job Number 4408, Drawing Number 905 (Folder 191)
      1 R.H. Car as Shown, Inside Elevation, Front of Cab, Rear Wall, Side Wall, Ceiling, Shaft Side Doors Shown, # 1-Written on the Back in Pencil, Elevator Doors and Front CAB, 37"x26 1/4", Paper, # 2-37 1/4"x26 1/4", Photocopy Paper, Architects, Rogers and Butler, Otis Elevator Company
    - 1/19/1908, Order Number 8780, # 561 (Folder 191)
      No Title, Front and Side Elevation, Plan, Elevator, Written on the Back in Pencil, Ash Hoist, 17 1/4"x22", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Sedgwick Machine Works
    - 6/14/1940, 111980 (Folder 191)
      One Electric Dumbwaiter, Automatic Call and Send Operation, 150#@ 90 F.P.M., 35 3/4"x23 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Otis Elevator Company
    - 7/9/1940, 111980-CL (Folder 192)
      Conduit Layout-D/W (Dumb Waiter) Controller, # 6-1F6123A, 8 1/2"x11", Paper (black and white), Architects, Otis Elevator Company
    - 6/24/1940, 111980-MB (Folder 192)
      Layout and Details for Erection of Rails-Brackets and Sheave Beams, Section Showing Erection of Rails and Brackets {Elevator Rails}, 27 1/8"x21 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Otis Elevator Company
    - undated, B21 Second Copy Doesn't Have a B# (Folder 192)
      Plan of Enclosure Around Service Elevator Machinery, # 1-@ 21"x23 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-@ 22"x23 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
      Received 10/8/1908 Charles T. Wills
    - undated, B22 (Folder 192)
      Enclosure Around Elevator Machinery, Section Through Line "A-A" (Looking North), 20 1/4"x25", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
    - undated, B23 Second Copy Doesn't Have a B# (Folder 193)
      Enclosure Around Elevator Machinery, Elevation Looking West, # 1-20 1/4"x25", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-18 78/"x21 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
    - undated, B25 (Folder 193)
      Enclosure Around Elevator Machinery, Elevation Looking North, 16 7/8"x22 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
    - 9/12/1951, Job Number E-0729, Sheet 1 of 2 (Folder 194)
      L.H. Swing Entrances, Full Scale Details at Head, Full Scale Detail at Jamb, # 1- Written on Back in Pencil, 1 E 75 St Service Elev., 30 3/8"x24", Paper, Blue Ink # 2-Approval Stamp (red ink) 10/21/1951, Written on the Back in Pencil, Superior Details Service Elevator, 30 1/4"x24", Paper, Blue Ink, # 3 and # 4-30"x24", Photocopy Paper (copy of drawing # 1), # 5 and # 6-30"x24", Photocopy Paper (copy of drawing # 2), Architects, Superior Fireproof Door and Sach Co., Inc. and Otis Elevator Company
    - 9/12/1951, Job Number E-0729, Sheet 2 of 2 (Folder 195)
      Full Scale Detail at Head, Full Scale Detail at Jamb, Section at 4th and 3rd Floors, Car Sill, Note on Right Side, # 1-30 1/4"x24", Paper, Blue Ink, # 2 and # 3-30"x24", Photocopy Paper (copy of drawing # 1), Architects, Superior Fireproof Door and Sach Co., Inc. and Otis Elevator Company
    - 10/16/1951, Job Number 51 E-0729, Sheet 2A (Folder 196)
      Second Floor Entrance, Section, R.H. Swing Entrance, Detail at Head, Jamb Details: At Pivot Side and At Lock Side, # 1-Approval Stamp (red ink) 30"x24", Paper, Blue Ink, # 2-Written on the Back in Pen, Pass-Elev-2nd Fl Entrance, 30 1/4"x24", Paper, Blue Ink, # 3 and # 4-30"x24", Photocopy Paper (copy of drawing # 2), Architects, Superior Fireproof Door and Sach Co., Inc. and Otis Elevator Company
    - 10/16/1951, Job Number 51 E-0729, Sheet 2B (Folder 197)
      First Floor Entrance, Section, R.H. Swing Entrance, Detail at Head, Jamb Details: Rivet Side and Lock Side, Note on Right Side # 1-Written on the Back in Ink, Pass Elev 1st Fl Entrance 1 75 St, 30 1/4"x24", Paper, Blue Ink, # 2-Approval Stamp (red ink) 10/25/51, 30 1/8"x24", Paper, Blue Ink, # 3 and # 4-30"x24", Photocopy Paper (copy of drawing # 2), Architects, Superior Fireproof Door and Sach Co., Inc. and Otis Elevator Company
    - undated, No Number (Rolled with B21-B23) (Folder 193)
      Enclosure Around Elevator Machinery, Section Through Line "B-B" (Looking North), @21 1/4"x24 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
    - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 189)